{
    "subject": "Ann_Smith_Franklin",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "James_Franklin__printer_",
    "human_readable": "Ann Smith Franklin is married to James Franklin (the printer).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9356666207313538,
            "question": "Is Ann Smith Franklin married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.852579653263092,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Ann Smith Franklin and printing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.850271463394165,
            "question": "Who is married to James Franklin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114816546440125,
            "question": "What is Ann Smith Franklin's relationship to James Franklin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7087357640266418,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the relationship between Ann Smith Franklin and James Franklin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5707501769065857,
            "question": "What is the name of James Franklin's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5376357436180115,
            "question": "Who is James Franklin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43411511182785034,
            "question": "What is Ann Smith Franklin's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3482988178730011,
            "question": "Who is known as 'the printer'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19329968094825745,
            "question": "What does James Franklin do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ann Smith Franklin is married to James Franklin (the printer).",
            "html": "yago_8889_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known as 'the printer'?",
            "html": "yago_8889_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ann Smith Franklin's profession?",
            "html": "yago_8889_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is James Franklin?",
            "html": "yago_8889_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8889_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Ann Smith Franklin is married to James Franklin (the printer).\" Specifically, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8889/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt mentions their marriage on 4 February 1723 and that he was a printer. Additionally, other documents detail the business they ran together and how Ann continued his printing business after his death."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}